Hannah Starcevich

(425) 698-8808 | starcevichh@gmail.com | Seattle, WA 98102

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/hannah-starcevich | GitHub: www.github.com/HannahStarcevich |

Portfolio: www.hannah-starcevich.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with a previous career as a Project Management Consultant at Microsoft (2.5 years). I am known by clients and peers for my sharp attention to detail, big picture planning skills and motivation to deliver high quality work. Excellent communication and presentation skills developed from consulting diverse audiences, including C-Level Executives, and teaching English throughout Latin America.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap
- GIT, GitHub, Terminal
- JavaScript, jQuery, Node.Js.
- AJAX, APIs, JSON

- React.js, React, React Hooks
- MySQL, Sequelize, Mongo DB

Relevant Experience & Projects

Pizza Cutter Website & Admin Dashboard | Full Stack Developer | Deployed Site | Github Link

Built a new modern site for Pizza Cutter restaurant with menu items stored in MySQL / Sequelize database. Including login portal for the owner to update menu item details and photos through an admin dashboard.

- Role: Led four person team as a project manager and coded both front and back end. Leverage ERD framework for database structuring with full CRUD functionality of menu items that dynamically update the customer facing site
- **Utilized**: Heroku, Sequelize, MySQL, Bcrypt, Express, Express-Session, Cloundinary, Dotenv, Node, Javascript, jQuery, JSON, Handlebars, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Materialize, GitHub, Git

Dynamic Full-Stack Burger Application | Full Stack Developer | Deployed Site | Github Link

Utilize this application to generate a list of hamburgers that are "ready to eat" or already eaten or "devoured". From the burgers that are "ready to eat" select those that you want to "devour!".

- Role: Independently developed full stack application launched on Heroku, including a MySQL database and Handlebars front-end framework to dynamically update elements to the page. Features RESTful conventions, model-view-controller file structuring and CRUD functionality
- **Utilized**: Heroku, MySQL, Node, Express, Handlebars and ORM. HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, JSON, GitHub, Git

In the Moment - Event & Brewery Finder | Front End Developer | Deployed Site | Github Link

A web app to search for events in a specific city based on TicketMaster API and discover unique breweries near the venue.

- Role: Developed a comprehensive application as the project manager, including JavaScript search engine developer, CSS lead developer. Used JSON / local storage to store API information and dynamically update page elements.
- Utilized: HTML, CSS, Foundation, Javascript, jQuery, Server-side APIs, AJAX, JSON, GitHub, Git

Professional Experience

Project Management Consultant - Microsoft Corporation, Redmond, WA (Contracted with <u>AG Consulting Partners</u>) 8/2018 - 11/2020

Led project management for global Enterprise sales strategy teams at Microsoft.

- Accelerated team success as the business manager of the Senior Director of Enterprise Commercial.
- Led all weekly team meetings for 12 senior business executives and drove momentum across global programs.
- Managed virtual events and program planning for global networks of thousands of Microsoft sellers.

- Led operations and logistics for the Enterprise Commercial quarterly business review cycle for 14 global regions.
- Created communications (PowerPoint and Email) distributed to thousands of Microsoft employees and Partners.
- Synthesized complex data sets to generate advanced PowerBi and Excel reports to inform global strategy.

Led the end to end project management of the development and launch of the AG Consulting Partners Website.

- Identified project scope, created and pitched the website map, content and design to the CEO and partners.
- Interviewed and selected website development team and led partnership through three-month design process.
- Orchestrated the company wide photoshoot and selected all media and images for the site.
- Launched site, maintained content updates such as blog articles and regular updates.

Led pro-bono consulting project, website site design and project management of Ben's Fund Non-Profit Website.

- Led six-month pro-bono consulting project and managed company wide support of the project.
- Designed the site mock up and pitched the site design to the Non-Profit owners and investors.

Volunteer & Work Experience in Latin America

NGO Program Ambassador—Days for Girls International, Panajachel, Guatemala	12/2018
Patagonia National Park Expedition Guide—Tierra Patagonia, Torres del Paine, Chile	12/2017 –
4/2018	
English Language Teacher—Beyond English & Independent Contractor, Santiago, Chile	2/2017 - 12/2017

Education

Full Stack Web Development Certificate

Coding Boot Camp, University of Washington Seattle, WA

10/2020 - 3/2021

9/2012 - 6/2016

Bachelor of Business Administration

University of Washington Foster School of Business, Seattle, WA

- Certificate of International Business: Spanish Track
- Centro de Idiomas: University of Washington, Spanish Study Abroad Program Leon, Spain